

PROFILE

Want to put your own image in the circle? It is easy! Select the image and do a right mouse click. Select "Fill" from the shortcut menu. Choose Picture... from the list. Navigate your computer to get the appropriate picture. Click okay to insert your selected image.

Once your image has been inserted, select it again. Go to the Picture Tools Format menu. Click on the down arrow below "Crop" and select "Fill" from the list. This will auto adjust your image to crop to the image. You can click and drag your image to place it appropriately.

CONTACT

PHONE: 0929-522-5777

WEBSITE PORTFOLIO LINK:

https://jndelacruz0420.github.io/jnbdc portfolio/

EMAIL:

Delacruziohnnoel0922@amail.com

HOBBIES

Playing online games Watching movies Travel

JOHN NOEL B. DELA CRUZ

Web Developer

EDUCATION

San Juan National High School

2008 - 2012

P. Narciso St. Brgy. Corazon De Jesus San Juan City

Polytechnic University of the Philippines

2012 - 2014, 2017 - 2019

Bachelor of Science Information Technology (Graduate)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pierre and Paul Solutions Inc. Software Developer (Intern)

Dec 2018 - March 2019

- Developed useful office software application using Laravel 5
- Developed PPSI Empcator and Accounting system

Cloudlogic Web Developer

Apr 2019 - Current

- Developed top brands E-commerce website in the Philippines with responsive design
- Contributed to back-end experience and collaborated on APIs.

SKILLS

- MySQL
- Google Analytics
- iQuery
- Project management
- CSS
- JavaScript
- HTML
- Ajax
- MVC Frameworks